hi i'm kenisha lee
red carpet makeup artist and beauty
activist and today i'm doing a product
review on two
products pure minerals um which
is a company that i actually interviewed
with a month ago
and before i went to interview with them
i wanted to find out
what their products were all about so
that i knew
that i would be able to represent their
company and brand
with integrity i went out and bought it
at alto which is where i believe
they are sold and i found that i
actually really really liked it
so enjoy this product review and we will
see you
for the next one i got the deeper which
i believe is their darkest shade
of the foundation that they have and
luckily
i'm about the darkest shade that they
actually
accommodate so uh sorry ladies if anyone
is darker than i am but they do have
some lighter shades that i think would
work
um for you if you are so inclined to go
and get this product
then i also picked up their mineral glow
which
is a bronzing powder that also matches
my
skin quite well and this is it comes in
this
um one i really enjoyed the fact that
the liquid came in a glass bottle and
not a plastic bottle
that i found was genius you know
i think it preserves better when it's in
a glass container than
a plastic container and the
mineral powder the packaging was okay i
mean it wasn't anything that stood out
or
was like striking for me but overall the
product itself
is really really good so i'm going to do
a demonstration
of the product itself and show you how
well it covers
um first of all i'm putting a little bit
of the
liquid foundation on my hand which is
usually how i apply my
foundation anyway i put it on the back
of my hand
usually once i get out of the showers
when i start to do my makeup
and i use this brush it's i consider it
my foundation fresh a lot of people will
use it for powder and things like that
but i use it for liquid and
i generally am doing this in the
bathroom
so i don't have a cup of water i usually
just run the water in the sink
but i dip my um i'm going to dip my
brush in the water and i'll show you
how well this actually covers and it's
such a good
nice consistency i also use this brush
because i don't like
a really heavy heavy heavy coverage i
like for the texture of my skin to come
through
and because this is full coverage it
tends to be a little bit thicker
than those that were light you know like
not a full coverage foundation
so we'll see here
and a little bit goes a really long way
i know you could see all of
my imperfections when we first started
and i'm not opposed to imperfections not
at
all but what i love love love and what
i've found in this last month
that i love about this foundation is the
four in one
is really something that
will heal your skin in the process and
that's what i've been finding is
happening
my skin has actually been healing and so
what we all want is nice clear skin
and so this product actually works to
help you
heal the skin
it's a 14 hour wear which
i think is another reason why it helps
to heal the skin as well
because you're not constantly reapplying
and putting stuff over stuff during the
day
so that's another advantage there
so pretty soon you'll see i'll be all
covered in this foundation
get a little more water to finish up the
lung pump that i put on my
hand
and then
i generally get underneath my chin as
well make sure that it's fully blended
and you see i'm going in a circular
motion
one more time last time
and then anything that i feel that i
want to super
hide or conceal i'll just use a little
bit more of
the product
and with my finger i will
press that into any of
the areas that i see is still not
covered
and then smooth it out
voila we have a full cupboard face
now we're gonna move on to their bronzer
which i
feel is amazing um
i like to use my smaller brush
applicator because i don't put this
all over my face i like to put it in the
spots where the sun will kiss my skin
first
which is generally just on on the bridge
of my nose
my cheekbones
which i have a lot of them
and
two other places my chin
here and then my nice forehead
and they have it a full covered face by
pure minerals which i really
think is a really superior product and
um you should go out and get some